rubbermaid.com 2010-05-07

# Rubbermaid Privacy Policy | Rubbermaid

Privacy

By using or accessing this website you signify your acknowledgment and assent to the Privacy Policy set forth below. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this website. Company can revise this policy at any time by updating this posting, and your use after such change signifies your acceptance of the changed terms. Please check these terms of use periodically for changes. 

This policy is intended to help you understand how Newell Rubbermaid Inc, its subsidiaries and affiliates ("Newell Rubbermaid," "we," or "us") collect, use and safeguard the information you provide on our website.

If you browse any Newell Rubbermaid website, you may generally do so anonymously without providing any personal information. However, there are cases in which we may ask you for personal data. For example, we will occasionally conduct on-line surveys to better understand the needs and profile of our visitors. In addition, we may request personal information when you register to receive additional information regarding our products and services, sign up for a newsletter, or send us a question. Even if you choose not to give information we request, you can still visit most of the Newell Rubbermaid website, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services.

In case you change your mind or wish to update or delete personal information (such as your zip code), we will endeavor to correct, update or remove the personal data you give us. You can do this by contacting us at the contact points specified below.

When you place an order for a product, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. This personal information is required so that we can process and fulfill your order, send an order or shipping confirmation, as well as notify you of your order status. All Internet transactions with Newell Rubbermaid are performed on a secure server that encrypts your credit card information to ensure it is not read by unauthorized third parties.

If you provide us with personal information, and choose to join a particular company's email list, we will place you on that company's list to receive e-mail regarding product updates, special offers, important issues and new products from that company as well as other subsidiary companies of Newell Rubbermaid. If you do not wish to receive e-mail updates, please contact us at the contact points specified below.

Personal information provided by users who are 13 or more years of age may be used for marketing and promotional purposes only by Newell Rubbermaid and its subsidiaries and affiliates. Newell Rubbermaid does not rent, sell or otherwise distribute to third parties, your personal information entered on this site without your consent, unless required by law or as disclosed to you when the information is collected. If you do provide us with consent to share your information with other companies, we may share your information with companies who offer products and services that may be of interest to you. These companies may then contact you directly with product or sample offers, personalized offers and information, or to ask for your feedback on products and programs that they think may be of interest to you. While we use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, Newell Rubbermaid will have no liability for disclosure of any information obtained due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties. Newell Rubbermaid also reserves the right to change or update this policy, or any other policy or practice, at any time, with reasonable notice to users of its website. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the Newell Rubbermaid site.

We may share statistical or aggregated non-personal information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. This data is used to customize Newell Rubbermaid website content and advertising to deliver a better experience to our users

This site may use cookies for site administration purposes. If for any reason you wish to not take advantage of cookies, you may have your browser not accept them, although this may disable or render unusable some of the features of the Newell Rubbermaid website.

This website also may detect and use your IP address or domain name for internal traffic monitoring and capacity purposes or to otherwise administer our website. No personal information is obtained, rather just the patterns of usage of our various users may be tracked to provide you with improved service and content based on aggregate or statistical reviews of user site traffic patterns.

Newell Rubbermaid reserves the right to disclose user information in special cases, when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other Newell Rubbermaid website users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose personal information without notice to you in response to a subpoena or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to respond to an emergency situation.

Newell Rubbermaid encourages parents and guardians to monitor and participate in their children's online activities. Unless you are viewing a website directed specifically to children, no information should be submitted to this site by users under 13 years of age, and users under 13 years old are not allowed to register for newsletters, clubs or activities. In addition, users under 18 years of age are not allowed to make purchases or participate in contests, except for those specifically directed to children. Where appropriate, Newell Rubbermaid may ask you to indicate your age to verify compliance with these policies.

Newell Rubbermaid does not knowingly collect information from our guests under 13 years of age or provide any personally identifying information from such guests to any third party for any reason whatsoever. We do not allow guests known to be under 13 years of age to receive direct marketing communications from Newell Rubbermaid or from third parties.

Please be advised that our website may contain links to third-party websites. The linked sites are not under the control of Newell Rubbermaid, and we are not responsible for the contents or privacy practices of any linked site or any link on a linked site.

Questions about this privacy policy should be directed to :

E-Business Team  
Newell Rubbermaid, Inc.  
29 East Stephenson Street  
Freeport, IL 61032  

Questions about our products should not be directed to this address and will not be replied to.  
If you would like your email address removed from our database, please send an email to [optout@newellco.com](mailto:optout@newellco.com) and type the word " **Remove** " in the subject line.
